That's what happens. Now, a really cool thing that happens from being
able to see something called reflections and a reflection is basically a
live feedback of your flows over time.
Over the last seven days, so it's always a weekly reflection and
you can always hover over this and click and it'll show you
kind of how this works specifically.
But now, my main thing is embracing stillness amidst pressure. This week,
you have shown a strong desire to align your action with God's
timing and presence.
You recognize that preparation is essential, but you also recognize that. See
how it can become a means of control rather than a way
to connect with God.
So I have these, this, this statement that gets updated. I have
my signals for the week and it shows me what flows they're
coming from.
And then down here, it gives me I am statements. So these
are things for me to declare to myself to make sure I,
make sure manifest this in reality of what I'm trying to do.
I'm learning to trust God's timing over my urgency. I'm embracing stillness
as a necessary part of my preparation. I'm committed to expressing gratitude
for my accomplishments.
I'm recognizing how self-imposed pressure affects my peace. All of these things
are true to me because these, this is my scripture.
This is what I've written through Bible, Bible flows and prayer flows.
This is what I've written through my own flows.
And then as you can see down here, it gives us all
of those flow histories. And it's always going to keep a history
of you and continue that you down that path.